movingworlds.org 2019-12-30

# MovingWorlds Privacy Policy | MovingWorlds.org

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for Movingworlds.org (the “Site”), owned and operated by MovingWorlds, SPC (referred to herein as “MovingWorlds”, “us” or “we”). We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the “User”) and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at [info@movingworlds.org](mailto:info@movingworlds.org).

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE.

## **Changes to Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of the Site. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Site. It is the responsibility of each User to review the Site and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

## **What types of information do we collect?**

We collect two types of information about our Site Users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

### **Personally Identifiable Information.**

Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific end user. We ask you for this information when you create an account on Site as an Experteer or an organization. Some of the information requested includes your name, country, languages spoken, mailing address, email address, gender, work history, education, etc. At the time of the request, this information will be identified as either mandatory or voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information, you will not be permitted to create an Account and use the Site.

### **Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**

Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific end user. We collect this information automatically. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the Site you visited before coming to our Site, the URL of the site you visit after leaving our Site, what pages you have accessed in our Site, how many times you clicked on specific areas, and where you clicked during your navigation, the type of owser you are using, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. Our mobile application automatically collects your phone’s operating version and operating system version.

## **How do we collect this information?**

All the personally and non-personally identifiable information is collected via one of the following methods:

  1. Users inputting their data into our system, including data they input while creating an account, using our online chat forum, and messaging services.
  2. If you allow the LinkedIn connect feature, we may copy some information from your LinkedIn account. You will be notified as to what this information is before approving the connection.
  3. Billing information is collected using Stripe ([http://www.stripe.com](https://stripe.com/)).
  4. Cookies for tracking site usage and visit. See _“Do we use Cookies?”._

## **How do we use the information collected?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, chat/message with other parties when online, click on a third party link, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the Site, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To authenticate users and their profile information
  * To perform services, i.e., allow you to create an account, upload and display information and photos regarding your expertise or organization, and match up Experteers to non-profit organizations
  * To allow for payment for our services
  * To improve the Site’s functionalities
  * To improve our services and make them more targeted to customer needs
  * To troubleshoot your specific problems

## **How do we protect information collected?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible to a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Site, and we are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

## **Do we use "Cookies"?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the introductions you request. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox) settings. Each owser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

## **Do we disclose the information we collect to third parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to third parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "third parties" does not include MovingWorlds, its affiliates, parent or subsidiary corporations. It also does not include Site hosting partners such as [Amazon Web Services](http://aws.amazon.com/) and [Stripe](https://stripe.com/), and other parties who assist us in operating our Site, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others' rights, property, or safety.

## **How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?**

Users may edit their personal information by directly making those changes in their online account and profile. These changes will be permanent. Also, you may choose to display only specific personal information by making those choices in your account settings. 

In addition, any user may request to delete their full account and all related data records from our external and/or internal systems for any unspecified reason, which will subsequently be processed without undue delay.

Please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request, only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. Moreover, you will not be able to delete the personal information, which is mandatory to maintain your Account, without cancelling your Account.

## **Third party links**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our Site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

## **Miscellaneous Privacy Issues**

### **Minors:**

Minors under the age of 13 (18 for residents of Florida) may not use the Site. We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be a minor, and no part of the Site is designed to attract a minor. If you are under the age of 13 (18 in Florida), you may use MovingWorlds.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Also, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.

### **International Transfer of Data:**

Our Site is hosted in the United States. If you visit our Site from Latin America, European Union, Asia, or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from United States law, please be aware that you are transferring personal information to United States. By providing personal information to us, you consent to the transfer of it to United States and the use of it in accordance with this policy.

### **Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents:**

California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (the “Act”) and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by the Act, we will provide you with the categories of Personally Identifiable Information that we collect through the Site and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such Personally Identifiable Information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at your request. California law requires us to inform you, at your request, (1) the categories of Personally Identifiable Information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies. The Act further requires us to allow you to control who you do not want us to share that information with. To obtain this information, please send a request by email to [info@movingworlds.org](mailto:info@movingworlds.org), or by standard mail to the Corporate Address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personally Identifiable Information you do not want us to share with Affiliated Businesses or Marketing Partners. The request should be labeled “California Customer Choice Notice.” Please allow 30 days for a response. Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your Personally Identifiable Information or requesting this notice.

## **Online Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our Site and not to information collected offline.

## **Terms of Use**

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site.

## **Contact Us**

We also welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issues to [info@movingworlds.org](mailto:info@movingworlds.org)

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 08, 2013.

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for Movingworlds.org (the “Site”), owned and operated by MovingWorlds, SPC (referred to herein as “MovingWorlds”, “us” or “we”). We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the “User”) and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at [info@movingworlds.org](mailto:info@movingworlds.org).
